

# **GLEB MURAWICKI**

**FULL STACK Developer** 

- ✓ discojordan23@gmail.com
- GDANSK, POLAND



Bē in 4







## **ABOUT**

Full Stack Developer with experience of 2 years. Was involved in the design and development of various websites. I have strong knowledge in HTML, CSS, SCSS, BEM Methodology, JavaScript, have experience in writing sites on WordPress. Inquisitive, constantly improving my skills, I find a common language with everyone. Ready to communicate in English. Also have useful skills in UX/UI, Graphic Design (more than 5 years of experience) and SEO.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML	CSS
JavaScript	SASS
React	Mongo
Express	Git
React Native	Figma
PhotoShop	Illustrator

#### **LANGUAGES**

English		B2
Polish		В1
Russian / Beloru	ussian NATI	VE

#### **COURSES**

<u>Front End Developer</u>	July 2022 - Mar 2023
JavaScript Intensive	Mar 2024
UX/UI Designer	Dec 2021 - May 2022
Google Analytics 4	Feb 2024

### **INTERESTS & HOBBIES**

Drawing on a graphic tablet **UX TESTING** Photographing Videomaking

#### **EDUCATION**

Sep 2019-May 2023

**Belarusian State University of Informatics** and Radioelectronics - Bachelor's degree

Faculty of Information Technology and Management, Speciality - Artificial Intelligence

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Front-End Developer / UX/UI Designer

Polotno Agency

May 2023 - Feb 2024

- Built more than 5 websites and web applications with the team. Held the role of UX/UI Designer and Front-End Developer.
- · Creation of multi-page, one-page websites, web applications in the role of Front-End Developer.
- · Cross-browser & adaptive website coding.

## Front-End Developer

Jordan Design Agency

Feb 2022 - Feb 2023

- · Landing site development
- · Development of sites on CMS such as WordPress, Tilda, etc.
- Development of sites on pure code, HTML / CSS / JS
- Development of adaptive sites

## Front-End Developer / SEO

Secondary School 36

Feb 2021 - May 2023

- Development, design and completion of the school website
- · Creating Graphic and Video works for contests.
- Design of social media profiles (Instagram, Telegram).
- · Designing posters, certificates, etc.
- · Worked with Search engine optimisation.
- · Preparing layouts for printing.